export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who was the first man created by God?",
    options: ["Noah", "Adam", "Abraham", "Moses"],
    correctAnswer: "Adam",
    category: "Old Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "How many days did Jesus fast in the wilderness?",
    options: ["20 days", "30 days", "40 days", "50 days"],
    correctAnswer: "40 days",
    category: "Gospels"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Who denied Jesus three times?",
    options: ["John", "Peter", "Matthew", "Andrew"],
    correctAnswer: "Peter",
    category: "Gospels"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What was the first plague of Egypt?",
    options: ["Frogs", "Water turned to blood", "Locusts", "Darkness"],
    correctAnswer: "Water turned to blood",
    category: "Old Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who wrote the most books in the New Testament?",
    options: ["John", "Peter", "Paul", "Luke"],
    correctAnswer: "Paul",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which disciple doubted Jesus's resurrection?",
    options: ["Thomas", "Peter", "John", "James"],
    correctAnswer: "Thomas",
    category: "Gospels"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What was the name of Moses's sister?",
    options: ["Miriam", "Ruth", "Rachel", "Sarah"],
    correctAnswer: "Miriam",
    category: "Old Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Who was thrown into the lions' den?",
    options: ["David", "Daniel", "Joseph", "Samuel"],
    correctAnswer: "Daniel",
    category: "Old Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "On which island was John when he wrote Revelation?",
    options: ["Cyprus", "Crete", "Patmos", "Malta"],
    correctAnswer: "Patmos",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Who was the first Christian martyr?",
    options: ["Stephen", "Paul", "Peter", "James"],
    correctAnswer: "Stephen",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What was Jesus' first recorded miracle in the Bible?",
    options: ["Healing a blind man", "Turning water into wine", "Raising Lazarus", "Healing a demon-possessed man"],
    correctAnswer: "Turning water into wine",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Who did Jesus heal with a touch of his cloak?",
    options: ["A leper", "A woman with bleeding", "A paralyzed man", "A blind man"],
    correctAnswer: "A woman with bleeding",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Which disciple witnessed Jesus walking on water?",
    options: ["Peter", "John", "All disciples", "Matthew"],
    correctAnswer: "All disciples",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "What was the condition of the man Jesus healed at the Pool of Bethesda?",
    options: ["Blind", "Lame", "Deaf", "Leprosy"],
    correctAnswer: "Lame",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "What was the name of the town where Jesus healed the blind and mute man?",
    options: ["Bethsaida", "Capernaum", "Nazareth", "Samaria"],
    correctAnswer: "Capernaum",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "Who did Jesus raise from the dead in Nain?",
    options: ["Lazarus", "Jairu's daughter", "The widow's son", "Tabitha"],
    correctAnswer: "The widow's son",
    category: "New Testament"
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "How long did Adam live?",
    options: ["120 years", "930 years", "600 years", "720 years"],
    correctAnswer: "930 years",
    category: "The Creation"
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "If we confess our sins He is faithful and just to forgive us our sins, and to clean us from all unrighteousness, can be find in?",
    options: ["John 3:14", "Romans 1:8", "1John 1:9", "Galatians 3:16"],
    correctAnswer: "1John 1:9",
    category: "Salvation"
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What did God create on the fifth day?",
    options: ["Fish and birds", "Animals", "Man", "Firmament"],
    correctAnswer: "Fish and birds",
    category: "Creation"
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "What was the serpent's punishment?",
    options: ["To lose its ability to speak", "To crawl on its belly", "To be cast out of Eden", "Death"],
    correctAnswer: "To crawl on its belly",
    category: "Creation"
  },
];